/* jshint esversion: 11 */

let animals = [
  {
    question: "How do you say a dog in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Mechka",
    choice2: "Mravka",
    choice3: "Kuche",
    choice4: "Kotka",
    answer: "Kuche",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a guinea pig in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Morsko svinche",
    choice2: "Morj",
    choice3: "Morsko konche",
    choice4: "Kotka",
    answer: "Morsko svinche",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a rabbit in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Mechka",
    choice2: "Zaek",
    choice3: "Kuche",
    choice4: "Jaba",
    answer: "Zaek",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a frog in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Jaba",
    choice2: "Mravka",
    choice3: "Kuche",
    choice4: "Kotka",
    answer: "Jaba",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a donkey in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Morsko svinche",
    choice2: "Mravka",
    choice3: "Kuche",
    choice4: "Magare",
    answer: "Magare",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a parrot in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Vulk",
    choice2: "Mravka",
    choice3: "Kuche",
    choice4: "Papagal",
    answer: "Papagal",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a chicken in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Pile",
    choice2: "Petel",
    choice3: "Mishka",
    choice4: "Magare",
    answer: "Pile",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a mouse in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Morsko svinche",
    choice2: "Kokoshka",
    choice3: "Kotka",
    choice4: "Mishka",
    answer: "Mishka",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a horse in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Magare",
    choice2: "Kon",
    choice3: "Kotka",
    choice4: "Zebra",
    answer: "Kon",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say a beaver in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Kamila",
    choice2: "Tigur",
    choice3: "Bobar",
    choice4: "Mishka",
    answer: "Bobar",
  },
];

let drinks = [
  {
    question: "How do you say tea in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Kafe",
    choice2: "Butilka",
    choice3: "Sok",
    choice4: "Chai",
    answer: "Chai",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say beer in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Bira",
    choice2: "Bora",
    choice3: "Chasha",
    choice4: "Kafe",
    answer: "Bira",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say wine in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Sok",
    choice2: "Vino",
    choice3: "Bira",
    choice4: "Chai",
    answer: "Vino",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say juice in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Chai",
    choice2: "Kafe",
    choice3: "Rakia",
    choice4: "Sok",
    answer: "Sok",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say pop in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Voda",
    choice2: "Bezalkoholno",
    choice3: "Sok",
    choice4: "Vino",
    answer: "Bezalkoholno",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say milk in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Kafe",
    choice2: "Mlyako",
    choice3: "Sok",
    choice4: "Chai",
    answer: "Mlyako",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say coffee in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Kafe",
    choice2: "Mlyako",
    choice3: "Sok",
    choice4: "Chai",
    answer: "Kafe",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say champagne in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Kafe",
    choice2: "Vino",
    choice3: "Bira",
    choice4: "Shampansko",
    answer: "Shampansko",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say hot chocolate in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Kafe",
    choice2: "Goresht shokolad",
    choice3: "Shokolad",
    choice4: "Chai",
    answer: "Goresht shokolad",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say sparkling water in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Voda",
    choice2: "Gazirana voda",
    choice3: "Sok ot portokal",
    choice4: "Bilkov chai",
    answer: "Gazirana voda",
  },
];

let colors = [
  {
    question: "How do you say black in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Cherveno",
    choice2: "Cherno",
    choice3: "Zeleno",
    choice4: "Byalo",
    answer: "Cherno",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say white in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Byalo",
    choice2: "Cherno",
    choice3: "Cherveno",
    choice4: "Julto",
    answer: "Byalo",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say yellow in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Cherveno",
    choice2: "Zeleno",
    choice3: "Oranjevo",
    choice4: "Julto",
    answer: "Julto",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say grey in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Sivo",
    choice2: "Oranjevo",
    choice3: "Zeleno",
    choice4: "Lilavo",
    answer: "Sivo",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say pink in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Lilavo",
    choice2: "Byalo",
    choice3: "Rozovo",
    choice4: "Cherno",
    answer: "Rozovo",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say green in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Byalo",
    choice2: "Zeleno",
    choice3: "Cherveno",
    choice4: "Julto",
    answer: "Zeleno",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say red in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Rozovo",
    choice2: "Cherno",
    choice3: "Cherveno",
    choice4: "Julto",
    answer: "Cherveno",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say orange in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Zeleno",
    choice2: "Cherno",
    choice3: "Cherveno",
    choice4: "Oranjevo",
    answer: "Oranjevo",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say brown in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Kafyavo",
    choice2: "Cherno",
    choice3: "Cherveno",
    choice4: "Julto",
    answer: "Kafyavo",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say blue in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Byalo",
    choice2: "Sinio",
    choice3: "Cherveno",
    choice4: "Julto",
    answer: "Sinio",
  },
];
let food = [
  {
    question: "How do you say soup in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Purjoli",
    choice2: "Supa",
    choice3: "Kufte",
    choice4: "Palachinka",
    answer: "Supa",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say ice cream in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Snqg",
    choice2: "Supa",
    choice3: "Sladoled",
    choice4: "Kufte",
    answer: "Sladoled",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say pancake in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Palachinka",
    choice2: "Desert",
    choice3: "Sladoled",
    choice4: "Pitka",
    answer: "Palachinka",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say bread in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Supa",
    choice2: "Hlyab",
    choice3: "Karnache",
    choice4: "Sladoled",
    answer: "Hlyab",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say toast in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Princesa",
    choice2: "Hlyab",
    choice3: "Karnache",
    choice4: "Bob",
    answer: "Princesa",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say stuffed turkey in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Pulnena puika",
    choice2: "Supa",
    choice3: "Kufte",
    choice4: "Pulneno pile",
    answer: "Pulnena puika",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say fries in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Purjoli",
    choice2: "Purjeni kartofi",
    choice3: "Purjeno kufte",
    choice4: "Palachinka",
    answer: "Purjeni kartofi",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say rice pudding in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Pile s oriz",
    choice2: "Mlyako s oriz",
    choice3: "Pastet",
    choice4: "Palachinka",
    answer: "Mlyako s oriz",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say salad in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Salata",
    choice2: "Supa",
    choice3: "Surma",
    choice4: "Sok",
    answer: "Salata",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say cake in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Torta",
    choice2: "Supa",
    choice3: "Tutmanik",
    choice4: "Krem",
    answer: "Torta",
  },
];
let phrases = [
  {
    question: "How do you say 'Hi' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Chao",
    choice2: "Mersi",
    choice3: "Zdravey",
    choice4: "Sujelyavam",
    answer: "Zdravey",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'Goodbye' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Chao",
    choice2: "Mersi",
    choice3: "Sujelyavam",
    choice4: "Zdravey",
    answer: "Chao",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'Sorry' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Sujelyavam",
    choice2: "Mersi",
    choice3: "Ne",
    choice4: "Da",
    answer: "Sujelyavam",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'No' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Da",
    choice2: "Dobre",
    choice3: "Mersi",
    choice4: "Ne",
    answer: "Ne",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'Yes' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Dobre",
    choice2: "Da",
    choice3: "Ne",
    choice4: "Moje",
    answer: "Da",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'Thank you' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Chao",
    choice2: "Blagodarya",
    choice3: "Zdravey",
    choice4: "Sujelyavam",
    answer: "Blagodarya",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'I cant' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Ne moga",
    choice2: "Mersi",
    choice3: "Neiskam",
    choice4: "Sujelyavam",
    answer: "Ne moga",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'See you later' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Chao",
    choice2: "Aide do posle",
    choice3: "Neznam",
    choice4: "Sujelyavam",
    answer: "Aide do posle",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'I dont know' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Ne razbiram",
    choice2: "Mersi",
    choice3: "Neiskam",
    choice4: "Neznam",
    answer: "Neznam",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say 'Whats your name' in Bulgarian?",
    choice1: "Kak si",
    choice2: "Kak se kazvash",
    choice3: "Kolko e chasa",
    choice4: "Sujelyavam",
    answer: "Kak se kazvash",
  },
];
